{
    "Questions": [
        {
          "question":       "Why does Bihar (you know who! ЁЯШЙ) look like you (Deep) ?",
          "optionOne":      "His mother and I played Dandiya!",
          "optionTwo":      "Because I masturbated into madam's mouth!",
          "optionThree":    "When madam shaved her beard tab main fisal gaya!",
          "optionFour":     "My dick's sweat dropped on madam.... that's why!",
          "rightAnswer":    "optionFour",
          "audiencePoll":   "5, 10, 5, 80, 0",
          "amount":         "5,000",
          "information":    "Deep ЁЯШН: It's pathologically not possible, madam's hole is so big, when she pees people thought 2-3 glaciers melted from Himalaya. ЁЯЩПЁЯЩПЁЯЩП"
        },
        {
            "question":    "Why does Deep prefer to travel in auto-rickshaw ?",
            "optionOne":   "In cabs and cars people fart and close the doors!",
            "optionTwo":   "when I hire oyo rooms with Pogo auto drivers don't ask for threesome",
            "optionThree": "Juggling boobs and heat from ass are my vitamins",
            "optionFour":  "Sometimes if I pay auto-drivers тВ╣ 10 more, they open their pants and bend!",
            "rightAnswer": "optionThree",
            "audiencePoll":"20, 5, 65, 15, 0",
            "amount":      "10,000",
            "information": "Deep ЁЯШЬ: рджрд┐рдорд╛рдЧ рднреА рддреВ, рдЦреЛрдкреЬреА рднреА рддреВ, рдореЗрд░реЗ рд▓рдВрдб рд╕реЗ рдЪреБрджреА рд╣реБрдИ рднреЛрд╕реЬреА рднреА рддреВред ЁЯЩПЁЯЩПЁЯЩП"
        },
        {
            "question":    "A woman was dead with swollen ass in KR Puram, why Deep was arrested ?",
            "optionOne":   "Deep thought it's Rubini Omkumar and shoved his weapon down!",
            "optionTwo":   "Kyunki uski gaand mein teetar ka baal aur udta teer tha",
            "optionThree": "Deep ne Bannerghatta mein churri chodi aur wo aurat ki gaand KR puram mein mari",
            "optionFour":  "Bhenchod! ye kya options hain!",
            "rightAnswer": "optionThree",
            "audiencePoll":"15, 5, 65, 5, 0",
            "amount":      "20,000",
            "information": "Deep ЁЯджтАНтЩВя╕П: рдЪреЛрдж рдЪреЛрдж рдХрд░ рддреБрдЭреЗ рд░рд╛рдВрдб рдХрд░ рджреВрдБ, рдЪрдмреВрддрд░реЗ рдЬреИрд╕реА рддреЗрд░реА рдЧрд╛рдВрдб рдХрд░ рджреВрдБ| ЁЯЩПЁЯЩПЁЯЩП"
        },
        {
            "question":    "What is the most shocking thing Deep observed in Epicor in his tenure of 5 Years ?",
            "optionOne":   "Deep saw Rubini Omkumar peeing with him in men's room fountains",
            "optionTwo":   "When madam had diarrhea, her seat had yellow wet stains from her wet fart!",
            "optionThree": "After meeting Chaudhary, Deep knows how 'asshole' looks like",
            "optionFour":  "Deep got to know that madam has a third nipple which turns him on!",
            "rightAnswer": "optionFour",
            "audiencePoll":"5, 2, 3, 90, 0",
            "amount":      "40,000",
            "information": "Deep ЁЯТЛ: Aai shapath, Her third nipple gives me a burj khalifa like erection. ЁЯЩПЁЯЩПЁЯЩП"
        },
        {
            "question":    "How did Deep wish happy birthday to Binod ?",
            "optionOne":   "Come and give a hug to Daddy!",
            "optionTwo":   "I really miss your gaand!",
            "optionThree": "When Binod asked for ice cream, Deep dimmed the lights and gave him a taste of his weapon!",
            "optionFour":  "рдЗрд╕рдХреА рдЧрд╛рдВрдб рд╣реИ рдЧрдЯрд░, рд╕рдм рдЗрд╕рдореЗрдВ рдореВрддрд┐рдпреЗ, рд╣реИрдкреНрдкреА рдмрд░реНрдердбреЗ рдмрд┐рдиреЛрдж рдЪреВрддрд┐рдпреЗред",
            "rightAnswer": "optionFour",
            "audiencePoll":"12, 18, 15, 65, 0",
            "amount":      "80,000",
            "information": "Deep ЁЯР▒тАНЁЯЪА: рдЦреЗрд▓рддрд╛ рд╣реВрдБ рдореИрдВ рдЬреБрдЖ рдФрд░ рд╕рдЯреНрдЯрд╛, рдмрд┐рдиреЛрдж рднреЬрд╡рд╛ рдореЗрд░рд╛ рд▓рдЯрдХрд╛ рд╣реБрдЖ рдЯрдЯреНрдЯрд╛. ЁЯЩПЁЯЩПЁЯЩП"
        },
        {
            "question":    "Which one of the four alternatives Deep will choose ?",
            "optionOne":   "When I saw Chaudhary first I thought He is a Shemale",
            "optionTwo":   "Wrestler has and is a pussy!",
            "optionThree": "Sandwich massage between Binod and Chaudhary!",
            "optionFour":  "Madam's offer: рдЖрдУ рдХреБрдЫ рдЦреЗрд▓реЛ, рдореИрдВ рдЯрд╛рдВрдЧ рдЙрдард╛рдКрдВ рддреБрдо рдкреЗрд▓реЛ |",
            "rightAnswer": "optionFour",
            "audiencePoll":"8, 5, 25, 62, 0",
            "amount":      "1,60,000",
            "information": "Deep ЁЯд│: What to do guys ? I love madam. My motto is \"рдХрджреНрджреВ рдорд┐рд▓реЗ рддреЛ рдХрд╛рдЯ рд▓реЛ, рдЪреВрдд рдорд┐рд▓реЗ рддреЛ рдЪрд╛рдЯ рд▓реЛ|\". ЁЯЩПЁЯЩПЁЯЩП"
        },
        {
            "question":    "When a gust of wind blew madam's dress in air, what was Deep's reaction ?",
            "optionOne":   "I feel acid in my eyes!",
            "optionTwo":   "рдЙреЬрддреА рд╣реИ рдлреНрд░реЙрдХ рдХрдгреНрдЯреНрд░реЛрд▓ рдореЗрдВ рд░рдЦреЛ, рдЪрдбреНрдбреА рди рдкрд╣рдиреЛ рдирд╛ рд╕рд╣реА рдЧрд╛рд░реНрдбрди рддреЛ рд╕рд╛реЮ рд░рдЦреЛ|",
            "optionThree": "Itna bada ??",
            "optionFour":  "Arri maiyya ri! kya dekh liya ye!",
            "rightAnswer": "optionTwo",
            "audiencePoll":"12, 78, 5, 5, 0",
            "amount":      "3,20,000",
            "information": "Deep ЁЯОГ: рдЙрд╕рдХреА рдлреНрд░реЙрдХ рдЙреЬреА рддреЛ рдЪреМрдмрд╛рд░рд╛ рдиреЫрд░ рдЖрдпрд╛, рдзреНрдпрд╛рди рд╕реЗ рджреЗрдЦрд╛ рддреЛ рдореИрдбрдо рдХрд╛ рд▓рдгреНрдб рджреЛрдмрд╛рд░рд╛ рдиреЫрд░ рдЖрдпрд╛|. ЁЯЩПЁЯЩПЁЯЩП"
        },
        {
            "question":    "Why does Pogo have a crush on Deep ?",
            "optionOne":   "Because рджреАрдк рдиреЗ рдЖрдЧ рд▓рдЧрд╛рдИ рдЭрд╛рдБрдЯреЛрдВ рдореЗрдВ рдЧреЛрдЯреЗ рд╕реБрд▓рдЧ рдЧрдП, рджреАрдк рдХрд╛ рдЬрдм рдкреЛрдЧреЛ рдиреЗ рджреЗрдЦрд╛ рдЙрд╕рдХреЗ рд▓реМреЬреЗ рд▓рдЧ рдЧрдП|",
            "optionTwo":   "Because before performance, Deep watches BDSM porn",
            "optionThree": "What the hell is this ? Can I kill you guys ?",
            "optionFour":  "Because Deep ko dekh ke Pogo ki jhaant bhi khadi ho jaati hai",
            "rightAnswer": "optionOne",
            "audiencePoll":"42, 8, 15, 15, 20",
            "amount":      "6,40,000",
            "information": "Deep ЁЯд│: Deep ne jab hathiyaar dikhaaya, Pogo sihar gayi, choot to phati hi thi uski, bhencho gaand bhi phat gayi. ЁЯЩПЁЯЩПЁЯЩП"
        },
        {
            "question":    "If it is raining heavily and there is no shelter, what would Deep do ?",
            "optionOne":   "Take shelter under Chaudhary's armpits",
            "optionTwo":   "What better place than Rubini Omkumar's pussy",
            "optionThree": "Under madam's fat ass",
            "optionFour":  "you guys are so dead for having this farewell",
            "rightAnswer": "optionTwo",
            "audiencePoll":"8, 80, 8, 2, 2",
            "amount":      "12,50,000",
            "information": "Deep ЁЯдв: Her pussy is the place I have been, It's so big, there I can quarantine!. ЁЯЩПЁЯЩПЁЯЩП"
        },
        {
            "question":    "Who do you hate most after this farewell ?",
            "optionOne":   "Sumit",
            "optionTwo":   "Anand",
            "optionThree": "I hate all of you!",
            "optionFour":  "vaibhav & Milan",
            "rightAnswer": "optionThree",
            "audiencePoll":"2, 6, 88, 1, 3",
            "amount":      "25 Lakh",
            "information": "Deep ЁЯдв: Everybody! Saale sab ke sab mutthal ho tum log. ЁЯЩПЁЯЩПЁЯЩП"
        },
        {
            "question": "Imagine , You ,J , N , R and KukuttPalli are in same locked room , to survive you must do any of these?",
            "optionOne": "I'd rather kill myself than fucking them",
            "optionTwo": "Pee on J and wet fart on madam's face",
            "optionThree": "Sabke laude kaat lunga",
            "optionFour": "Madam ko chusa dunga",
            "rightAnswer": "optionThree",
            "audiencePoll": "5, 5, 85, 5",
            "amount": "5o Lakh",
            "information": "Deep screaming after answering this question -Gaand maar dunga sabki..Go lang se!"
        },
        {
            "question":    "What does Tilak like to take ?",
            "optionOne":   "Johnson ki choot jaisi shakal ki chummi",
            "optionTwo":   "Choot ke paani se bheega hua Varun ka Lund!",
            "optionThree": "Madam ke laudey se nikla moot jaisa peela paani",
            "optionFour":  "Pogo channel ki sookhi hui choot jismain ek baar lund daalne se chilaa jaaye!",
            "rightAnswer": "optionFour",
            "audiencePoll":"12, 15, 15, 58, 0",
            "amount":      "1 Crore",
            "information": "Tilak : Is sansaar mein choot se bada koi dharm nahi aur sookhi choot ko chilne jaisi badi koi ibaadat nahi!"
        },
        {
            "question":    "Tilak kya mooh mein leke nahi bolta hai ?",
            "optionOne":   "madam ka lauda!",
            "optionTwo":   "Johnson ka Lehsun",
            "optionThree": "Varun ki moong-fali",
            "optionFour":  "Main apna hi din bhar mooh mein liye ghoomta hum",
            "rightAnswer": "optionThree",
            "audiencePoll":"5, 18, 60, 15, 5",
            "amount":      "3 Crore",
            "information": "Tilak ЁЯШЫ: What to tell you guys, I am very flexible."
        },
        {
            "question":    "Which one is the religious tallest minar in India ?",
            "optionOne":   "Fateh Burj",
            "optionTwo":   "Qutub Minar",
            "optionThree": "Chand Minar",
            "optionFour":  "Shaheed Minar",
            "rightAnswer": "optionOne",
            "audiencePoll":"50, 15, 10, 15, 10",
            "amount":      "5 Crore",
            "information": "The Fateh Burj (English: The Victory Tower) is the tallest religious minar in India situated in the historical village of Chappar Chiri in the SAS Nagar district, Punjab. It was completed in 2011."
        },
        {
            "question":    "With how many countries India share its land borders ?",
            "optionOne":   "5",
            "optionTwo":   "6",
            "optionThree": "7",
            "optionFour":  "8",
            "rightAnswer": "optionTwo",
            "audiencePoll":"5, 90, 3, 2, 0",
            "amount":      "7 Crore",
            "information": "Inventor Ralph Baer, The 'Father Of Video Games,' Dies At 92. German-American game developer Ralph Baer shows the prototype of the first games console which was invented by him during a press conference on the Games Convention Online in Leipzig, Germany in 2009."

        }
      ]
    }